sandicor.com 2011-06-02

# Privacy Policy | Sandicor, Inc. - Your Source for MLS Property Data in San Diego County, California

Sandicor, Inc. (Sandicor) is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of consumers of its interactive products and services. Throughout cyberspace, we want to contribute to providing a safe and secure environment for consumers, and in particular, ensure that members' information is protected. 

The purpose of this Sandicor privacy policy is to inform you, as a welcome visitor to sandicor.com, what kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit sandicor.com, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, the information. Finally, please note that this policy applies only to Sandicor web sites that carry the Sandicor logo, and not to other companies' or organizations' web sites to which we link. We have clearly marked Sandicor and these branded web sites with our logo so you know where this policy applies.

## Information About All Sandicor Visitors

In general, our service automatically gathers certain usage information like the numbers and frequency of visitors to sandicor.com and its areas, very much like television ratings that tell the networks how many people tuned in to a program. We only use such data in the aggregate. This collective data helps us determine how much our customers use parts of the site, so we can improve our site to assure that it is as appealing as we can make it for as many of you as possible. For example, Sandicor.com uses a technology nicknamed "cookies" that tells us how and when pages in our site are visited, and by how many people. Sandicor.com cookies do not collect personally identifiable information and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personally identifiable information to tell us who you are or even what your e-mail address is. We also may provide statistical "ratings" information, never information about you personally, to our Sandicor partners about how our members, collectively, use Sandicor.com. We do this so they too can understand how much people use their areas and our site in order for them to provide you with the best possible Web experience as well.

## Information About You

Sometimes, we may specifically ask for information about you when you sign up to use or pay for a service. We will need certain information -- such as name, Internet address or screen name, billing address, type of computer, credit card number \-- in order to provide that service or product to you. We may ask you for information about your interests so that both you and we can take advantage of the interactivity of the online medium, but you may always choose to respond or not. 

## Disclosure

We do not use or disclose information about your individual visits to Sandicor.com or information that you may give us, such as your name, address, email address or telephone number, to any outside companies. But as we mention above, we may share with our web site partners aggregated statistical "ratings" information about the use of sandicor.com.

## Sandicor Privacy Policy Changes 

If we decide to change our privacy policy for sandicor.com, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. 

## Terms of Payment

By using this site to make a payment, you acknowledge the following:

Sandicor does not provide refunds, partial refunds or credits for any payments received for the key fee. The fee paid for key service is for a calendar year or a portion thereof. Sandicor reserves the right, at any time and without prior notification, to modify, alter, or update these terms. Continued use of this site confirms that you agree to the most current version of these terms.
